PERB Collective Bargaining Agreements from States other than New York 6065
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- State, County, & Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of. Local 1061 - Agreements (Box 7, Folder 29)
- State, County & Municipal Employees, Local 1083 - Agreements (Box 7, Folder 30)
- State, County and Municipal Employees, American Federation of, Local 1117 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- State, County and Municipal Employees Amer. Fed. Of Council 40, Local 1365 - Agreement (Box 7, Folder 32)
- State, County & Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of Local 1390, Lansing City Employees, Agreements (Box 7, Folder 33)
- State, County & Municipal Employees (Box 7, Folder 34)
- State, County and Municipal Employees Amer. Fed. Of Council 44, Local 1894 - Agreement (Box 7, Folder 35)
- State, County and Municipal Employees, American Fed. Of Council 64 - Agreements (Box 7, Folder 36)
- State, County & Municipal Employees, District Council 77 - Agreements (Box 7, Folder 37)
- State, County and Municipal Employees Amer. Fed. Of Council 75 - Agreement (Box 7, Folder 38)
- State, County and Municipal Employees Amer. Fed. Of Council 81, Local 1607 - Agreement (Box 7, Folder 39)
- State, County and Municipal Employees, American Fed. Of - Local 1659 1976-79 Agreement (Box 7, Folder 40)
- American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Council 4 Local 1716 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- State, County and Municipal Employees Amer. Fed. Of. Council 75, Local 1940 - Agreement (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Service Employees International Union, Local 660, Professional Accountants (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Service Employees International Union, Local 660/Social Services Union, 535 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Service Employees International Union, Local 660, Supervisory Administrative & Technical Staff Services, Personnel Unit (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Service Employees International Union, Local 660, Supervisory Artisan & Blue Collar Employees (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Service Employees Intl. Union Local 715 - Agreements (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Sheriff's Association of Ventura County - Agreements (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Sheriffs Dept., Assn. Kent County Agreements (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Sheriff's Dept. Command and Admn. Assn. Agreement (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Sheriff's Office Employees Assn. - Agreement (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Social Service Employees Assn., Washington County - Agreements (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Social Workers Organization of Agreement (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Special Services Union Local #461 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Spokane Police Guild Agreements (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Staff Nurses Council of Milwaukee (Box 8, Folder 14)
- State, County and Municipal Employees American Federation of, Psychiatric Social Workers (Box 8, Folder 15)
- State, County & Municipal Employees Dist. Council #3 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, District #33 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- State, County & Municipal Employees Dist. Council 47 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- State, County and Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of. District Council 48 - Agreement (Box 8, Folder 19)
- American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, District Council No. 51 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- State, County and Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of Council 67, Local 44 - Agreement (Box 8, Folder 21)
- State, County & Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of. Local 60 - Agreements (Box 8, Folder 22)
- State, County & Municipal Employees Amer. Fed. Of Local 87, Council 4 - Agreement (Box 8, Folder 23)
- State, County and Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of Council 75, Local 88 - Agreement (Box 8, Folder 24)
- State, Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of Local 101 Municipal Employees Fed. - Agreements (Box 8, Folder 25)
- State, County and Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of Local 101, Dayton Public Service Union - Agreements (Box 8, Folder 26)
- State, County and Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of, Local 117 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- State, County and Municipal Employees Council 36, Local 119 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- State, County and Municipal Employees, American Federation of, Council 36, Local 830 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- State, County and Municipal Employees Amer. Fed. Of Local 120-K - Agreement (Box 8, Folder 30)
- State, County & Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of. Local 122 - Agreements (Box 8, Folder 31)
- State, County and Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of. Local 146 - Agreements (Box 8, Folder 32)
- State, County and Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of Local 152 - Agreement (Box 8, Folder 33)
- State, County and Municipal Employees American Fed. Of Local 167 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- State, County & Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of. Local 192 - Agreements (Box 8, Folder 35)
- American Federation of State, County and Municipal employees, Local 251 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- State, County & Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of District Council 94 - Agreements (Box 9, Folder 1)
- State, County and Municipal Employees Amer. Fed. Of Local 1587 - Agreements (Box 9, Folder 2)
- State, County and Municipal Employees Amer. Fed. Of Council 23, Local 1659 - Agreement (Box 9, Folder 3)
- State, County and Municipal Employees, American Federation of Local 1733 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- State, County & Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of. Local 1919 - Agreements (Box 9, Folder 5)
- State, County & Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of. Local 1963 - Agreements (Box 9, Folder 6)
- State, County & Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of. Local 1992 - Agreements (Box 9, Folder 7)
- State, County & Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of. Local 2077 Library Employees Union - Agreements (Box 9, Folder 8)
- American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employee, District Council 20, Local 2091 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- State, County and Municipal Employees Council 67, Local 2202 - Agreement (Box 9, Folder 10)
- State, County & Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of. Local 2206 - Agreements (Box 9, Folder 11)
- State, County & Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of Local 2266 - Agreements (Box 9, Folder 12)
- State, County, and Municipal Employees American Fed. Of Local 2281 - Agreements (Box 9, Folder 13)
- State, County and Municipal Employees Amer. Fed. Of Local 2284 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- State, County, and Municipal Employees American Federation of Local 2287 - Agreement (Box 9, Folder 15)
- State, County & Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of Council 71, Local 2309 - Agreements (Box 9, Folder 16)
- State, County & Municipal Employees, Amer. Fed. Of. Local 2407 - Agreements (Box 9, Folder 17)
- State, County & Municipal Employees Local 2449 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- State, County and Municipal Employees American Fed. Of Local 2462 - Agreements (Box 9, Folder 19)
- State, County & Municipal Employees, American Federation of, Local 2700 (United Clerical Employees) (Box 9, Folder 20)
- State, County, and Municipal Employees American Fed. Of AFL-CIO Local 2735 - Agreements (Box 9, Folder 21)
- State, County and Municipal Employees Wayne County Engineering - Local 2926 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Supervisory Employees Association of Wayne County (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Supervisory Peace Officers (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Supervisory Professional Social Workers of Los Angeles County (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Surf Lifesaving Assn., Huntington Beach - Agreements (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Tacoma City Employees, Local #120 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Teamsters, Chauffers, and helpers Union Local 43 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers Union, Local #313 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Teamsters, International Brotherhood of Local 38 - Agreement (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Teamsters, Intl. Brotherhood of Local 145 - Agreements (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Teamsters, International Brotherhood of Local 102 - Agreement (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Teamsters, Intl. Brotherhood of Local 200 - Agreements (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Teamsters, Intl. Brotherhood of Local 214 - Agreements (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Teamsters, Intl. Brotherhood of Local 215 - Agreements (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Teamsters, Intl. Brotherhood of Local 242, Municipal Truck Drivers Union - Agreements (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Teamsters, International Brotherhood of Local 249 - Agreement (Box 9, Folder 37)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 270 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Teamsters, Intl. Brotherhood of Local 397 - Agreements (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Teamsters, Chauffeurs & Warehousemen, Intl. Brotherhood of Local 580 - 1979-1980 Agreement (Box 9, Folder 40)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 609, Refuse and Salvage Drivers and Helpers Local Union (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Teamsters, Intl. Brotherhood of Local 695 - Agreement (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Teamsters, Intl. Brotherhood of Local 957 - Agreements (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Teamsters, International Brotherhood of Local 980 - Agreement (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers Union, Local 313 - Agreements (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Teamsters, Laborers, Machinists and Operating Engineers (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Teamsters, Seattle Police Civilian Employees, Local 763 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Teamsters' State, County & Municipal Employees, Local 246 (Fairfax Cnty.) (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Technicians, Engineers and Architects of Milwaukee County (Box 9, Folder 49)
- Trades Council, Columbia Basin - Agreements (Box 9, Folder 50)
- Transit Union Division Local #758 (Box 9, Folder 51)
- Transit Union, Amalgamated Division 1027 - Agreements (Box 9, Folder 52)
- Transit Union Amalgamated Division 1293 - Agreements (Box 9, Folder 53)
- Transportation Union, United - Agreements (Box 9, Folder 54)
- Wayne County Dietician and Nutritionist Assoc. (Box 9, Folder 55)
- Wisconsin Education Association Council (Box 9, Folder 56)
- Colleges and Universities (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Ashland College (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Cook County College (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Eastern Illinois University (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Lowell State College (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Nebraska State College (Box 10, Folder 6)
- New Jersey College of Medicine and Dentistry (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Saginaw Valley College (Box 10, Folder 8)
- University of Toronto (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Vassar College (Box 10, Folder 10)
- University of Wisconsin (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Belleville Area College (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Central Michigan University (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Delaware University (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Dowling College (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Ferris State College (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Henry Ford Community College (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Lincoln University (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Massachusetts College of Art (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Monmouth College (New Jersey) (Box 10, Folder 20)
- New Jersey State Colleges (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Oakland University (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Pennsylvania State College (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Rhode Island University (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Roger Williams College (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Rutgers St. University (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Wayne State University (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Public Schools (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Andover Public Schools (Massachusetts) (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Beverly School Committee (Massachusetts) (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Boston School Committee (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Chicago Teachers Union (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Framingham School Committee (Massachusetts) (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Greater Anchorage Area Borough School District (Alaska) (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Manchester Bd. Of Ed. (Connecticut) (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Massachusetts Teachers Assoc. (Box 10, Folder 36)
- New Haven Bd. Of Ed. (Connecticut) (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Newark Bd. Of Ed. (New Jersey) (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Philadelphia School Dist. Bd. Of Ed. (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Pittsfield School Committee (Massachusetts) (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Springfield School Committee (Massachusetts) (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Warwick School Committee (Rhode Island) (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Los Angeles Building and Construction Trades Council (Box 11, Folder 1)
- California Assoc. of Professional Employees - Agreements (Box 11, Folder 2)
- California Association of Professional Employees - Agreements (Box 11, Folder 3)
- California Association of Professional Employees - Agreement (Box 11, Folder 4)
- California Association of Professional Employees - Agreements (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Association of Psychiatric Social Workers/American Federation of State County and Municipal Employees (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Social Services Union, Local 535 - Agreements (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Los Angeles County Employees Association 666, SEIU AFL-CIO (Box 11, Folder 8)
- American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Los Angeles County Employees Association, Local 660, SEIU AFL-CIO (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Joint Council of Social Services Union, Local 535 SEIU, Los Angeles County Employees Assn. (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Los Angeles County Profess. Peace Officers Association (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Amer. Fed, of State, County, and Municipal Employees (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Joint Council of Los Angeles County Employees Union, SEIU AFL-CIO Local 434, Local 666 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Los Angeles County Firefighters (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Joint Council of Los Angeles County Employees Association Local 660 Service Employees (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Los Angeles County Employees Union, SEIU AFL-CIO (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Professional Peace Officers Association (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Association of Los Angeles County Dental Personnel (Box 12, Folder 4)
- American Federation of State County and Municipal Employees Local 575 AFL-CIO (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Joint Council of Los Angeles County Public Health Association Local 660, SEIU (Box 12, Folder 6)
- International Union of Operating Engineers Local 501 AFL-CIO (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Los Angeles County Employees Association Local 660, Service Employees Intl. Union AFL-CIO (Box 12, Folder 8)